<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type = "text/xsl" href ="A01281743_3.xsl"?>
<inventory>
    <books>
        <book>
            <name>The Ballad of Songbirds and Snakes</name>
            <summary>
            The prequel of the Hunger Games series tells the story
            of a 18 year old Coriolanus Snow and his journey to obtain the Capitol's
            power.  
            </summary>
            <year>2020</year>
            <author>Suzanne Collins</author>
            <characters>
                <character>
                    <name>Coriolanus Snow</name>
                    <desc>
                    Main character of the book. He comes from a prestige family, but both
                    his parents died during war, leaving him with his cousin and grandma. He 
                    is chosen to be one of the mentors for the 10th Hunger Games, due to being 
                    poor and his desire to have power he becomes determined to make his tribute win.
                    </desc>
                </character>
                    <character>
                        <name>Lucy Gray Baird</name>
                        <desc>
                            She is the female tribute from District 12 and the mentee of Snow.
                            She is part of a musical group and has an enchanted singing voice.
                            Because of her beautiful voice she gains popularity among the Capitol's 
                            citizens and becomes one of the favorite to win. 
                        </desc>
                    </character>
                    <character>
                        <name>Sejanus Plinth</name>
                        <desc>
                            He is a mentor in the 10th Hunger Games. He is originally from District 2
                            but because of his father's job he moved the the Capitol. He is against all
                            it represents the Hunger Games and is disgusted to participate on them. Even
                            with that ideology he still mantains a friendship with Snow.
                        </desc>
                    </character>
            </characters>
        </book>
    </books>


    <tvshows>
        <show>
            <name>Sex Education</name>
            <premise>
                It follows Otis, an introvert teenage boy who knows a lot of sex. Maeve, a girl
                from his school saw how he helped another teen with his sexuality problems, she
                proposed Otis to open a business to help kids with their sexuality in exchange of money.
                Ots accepts and the show revoles around the different problems teens have.
            </premise>
            <year>2019</year>
            <creator>Laurie Nunn</creator>
            <characters>
                <character>
                    <name>Otis Milburn</name>
                    <desc>
                        An awkward teenager who becomes a sex therapist in his High School. Has 
                        a major crush on Maeve. 
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Maeve Wiley</name>
                    <desc>
                        She is an intelligent and a social outcast. She lives alone in her caravan
                        after all her family abandon her. She saw a way to get money by persuading Otis
                        to open a sex therapy business. 
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Eric Effiong</name>
                    <desc>
                        He is Otis' best friend, who is gay and is being bullied in school. He hasn't
                        told his family about his sexuality because they are religious.
                    </desc>
                </character>
            </characters>
        </show>

        <show>
            <name>Glee</name>
            <premise>
                Follows a chours or glee club from McKinely High School. The glee club is considered
                the lowest level of the social ladder in the school. So as they try to win Nationals, 
                the teens and their teacher need to fight the constant neglection and attacks from the 
                bullies and cheerleader coach.  
            </premise>
            <year>2009</year>
            <creator>Ryan Murphy</creator>
            <characters>
                <character>
                    <name>Will Schuester</name>
                    <desc>
                        He's the teacher or director of the glee club. When he was in high school he was
                        part of the glee club so he wants to inspire the kids and get them win Nationals.  
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Sue Sylvester</name>
                    <desc>
                        She is the cheerleader headcoach and wants to destory the glee club. Her main goal
                        throughout the series is bring down the glee club and Will.
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Rachel Berry</name>
                    <desc>
                        An ambitous, driven and talented girl who dreams of performing in Broadway. She is part
                        of the glee club and always wants the spotlight constantly fighting for the solos.
                    </desc>
                </character>
            </characters>
        </show>

        <show>
            <name>Teen Titans</name>
            <premise>
                A group of five teenager superheroes who are entrusted to take care of the city's safety
                from villians.
            </premise>
            <year>2003</year>
            <creator>Glen Murakami and Sam Register</creator>
            <characters>
                <character>
                    <name>Robin</name>
                    <desc>
                        He is the leader of the group. Although he doesn't have any superpower, he is a 
                        pro for the martial arts and hand-to-hand combats.
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Starfire</name>
                    <desc>
                        She is part of the Teen Titans. Her powers include: star bolts, star blats, laser-eyes, 
                        super strength and flying among others.
                    </desc>
                </character>
                <character>
                    <name>Beast Boy</name>
                    <desc>
                        He is part of the Teen Titans. His main power is to transform or change into any animal.
                        He is the jokester of the group.
                    </desc>
                </character>
            </characters>
        </show>
    </tvshows>

    <albums>
        <album>
            <name>Nothing Happens</name>
            <desc>
                Nothing Happens is the debut album of american band Wallows. The genre of the album is Indie Pop.  
            </desc>
            <year>2019</year>
            <performer>Wallows</performer>
            <songs>
                <song>
                    <name>Are you bored yet?</name>
                    <desc>
                        This song features female singer Clairo. The song talks about a partner being
                        bored in the relationship they have been in a while, but have the fear that the others
                        partner is also ready to move on.
                    </desc>
                </song>
                <song>
                    <name>Only Friend</name>
                    <desc>
                        This track is the first one of the album. It talks about losing innocence, and the move from
                        teenage years into adulthood. Also it can be interpreted as losing the one person that means
                        the most.
                    </desc>
                </song>
                <song>
                    <name>Do Not Wait</name>
                    <desc>
                        Is the final track of the album. Touches the theme of life. No matter what happens in life, or if you have
                        the biggest problem, at some point in your life, nothing happend and there's so much life ahead; everything's okay.
                    </desc>
                </song>
            </songs>
        </album>
    </albums>
</inventory>